<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Botches and Bodges on m2s docs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Botches and Bodges on m2s docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 22:18:45 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Burn Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/burnout/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 22:18:45 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/burnout/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is something i will add too overtime, but as i was writing out script goes beep i thought i needed to add some more context to why i end up being more &amp;lsquo;mean&amp;rsquo; in some of these stories.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Where normally &amp;ldquo;Why didn&amp;rsquo;t you just help them&amp;rdquo; would be a very fair statement.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;This will be directly linked when relevant&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On paper &amp;amp; in pay my role was a Standard T1 Tech role.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;In practice it ended up being a more T3/Sysadmin role. I Was managing most of the servers, WSUS, changing vlans on switches, Paxton, software deploy etc.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The really really hard stuff the Boss or Mr A did, but they only had a couple of hours a week on a good week where they could spend on technical issues.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intake Goes Bye Bye</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/intakegoesbyebye/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 21:45:21 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/intakegoesbyebye/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Another Late at the grammar story.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We stored student files in a way similar to this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;  &#xD;&#xA;  &#xD;&#xA;  &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;  &#xD;&#xA;  &#xD;&#xA;  &#xD;&#xA;  &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;  &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;prism-codeblock &#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;pre id=&#34;716cf3f&#34; class=&#34;language-text &#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;code&gt;\\DC1\Studnet\2018&#xD;&#xA;\\DC1\Studnet\2020&#xD;&#xA;\\DC2\Studnet\2017&#xD;&#xA;\\DC2\Studnet\2019&lt;/code&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/pre&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The year represents the year the student would be if they started at our school at Year 7 (11 years old by Aug 31st).&lt;br&gt;&#xA;At the time our retention policy was 7/8 years (the math is confusing as will be shown in this post).&lt;br&gt;&#xA;We went to Year 13, so it effectively it would be the August of year 14 if they stayed in school for the extra year (trying to explain the context rather than what happened).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(Noodle) Script Goes Beep</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/scriptgoesbeep/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 21:45:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/scriptgoesbeep/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sometime Late time at the grammar.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I Realize as i started to prep to write this out it may not paint be in the best of lights&amp;hellip;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;This person whom i didn&amp;rsquo;t help in this situation had &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;far beyond&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; what would be classed as normal support in learning the tools we used. Everyone in the dept had helped them at some point to learn this process.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;This included several &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;show&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;tell&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; walkthroughs of using this tool&lt;br&gt;&#xA;And a guide which i feel could be handed to almost anyone and if taught how to open powershell how it was needed could likely run this process.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;See also &lt;a data-bs-delay=&#34;{&amp;#34;hide&amp;#34;:300,&amp;#34;show&amp;#34;:550}&#34; data-bs-html=&#34;true&#34; data-bs-title=&#34;&lt;a href=&#39;http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/burnout/&#39;&gt;&lt;p&gt;BOTCHES AND BODGES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadcast Storm &amp; Missing Switch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/broadcaststorm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 19:57:16 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/broadcaststorm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Oct/Nov 2017&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Important context, this was a week or two into my first job.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Looking back I knew nothing.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;i&amp;rsquo;d been reading &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;a lot&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; of random stuff on Reddit, Stack etc to try and gain knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Due to its weird shape, and its size, the grammar school had many networking switches across the site. Some where up in nice cabs, others were shoved on the top of a shelf.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chips and Printers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/printerchip/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 21:45:16 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/printerchip/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, not the tasty kind&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;HP Printers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Do I Need to say more?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nearing the end of my time at the grammar school, the newly opened sports hall had a PE office in need of a printer, This was during Covid.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;We went with a colour HP Laser printer, I don&amp;rsquo;t remember the exact model number, but as I Wrote this up &amp;ldquo;M402dn&amp;rdquo; Came to mind and if its not that printer, its in the same family / group / model line (Whatever they are calling it this week ).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoking Out the Boss`s Boss</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/smokeyboi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 20:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/smokeyboi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Not with fire.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In My defence, I was told more smoke&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Smoke being the Glycole / Water based stuff that&amp;rsquo;s quite safe.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For some reason the smoke machine had been kept in the IT Office rather that with the drama department. And somehow I ended up agreeing to Running the smoke machine during a production of Greece.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I like the idea of all of the smoke, &lt;strong&gt;but&lt;/strong&gt; I Do try to be sensible, and not over do things like smoke. If you see the video bellow, that was taken during to testing, I thought I Was putting far to much smoke out. And yes, cameras do camera things and make it look a touch worse, but it was still quite thick.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire Muhaha (Playing With Matches)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/firemuhaha/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 20:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/firemuhaha/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Before I Start with this I Do have to mention 4 Things&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Bodgeit and Scarper Taught me this  (These will likely be mentioned in further stories)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It Was Safe / Risk Assessed (I Have written many fire related risk assessments)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do not try this at home (or work)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;This was done when I was the only person in the building&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, this is a useful know how to have, if you have the ability to do it safely without annoying facilities / setting off a fire alarm.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Note; Nothing crazy happens in this story, its just interesting enough to have its own page.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(Noodle) USB File Server Deletion</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/usbserver/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 16:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/usbserver/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;(nothing to do with viruses/crypto)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An important precursor to this is that Noodle was responsible for the backups. We used tape backups at the time: go into server room, shove in tape, check next day on the console it was ok, weekly restore test.  There was gaps of over a month at times.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;They kept &amp;ldquo;Forgetting&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And, we regularly went to &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;\\server\F$&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; to access things from the servers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I had just had a couple of days off for a reason, or if I Had been ill or whatever, but I Came into the backlash of this.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I had in my head this was the DC, but as I type it out if may have been our media server and I had been trying to migrate it and had an out of date copy there.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 AM Server updates</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/8amserver/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 16:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/whoops/8amserver/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Relatively early into my IT Career, say a year / 18 months, I rebuilt the WSUS server at my work.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Those who know the pain of WSUS know that to keep it working it needs to be rebuilt every now and then so it keeps working, and it hadn&amp;rsquo;t been working for a while so I took it on as a project.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Money&amp;rdquo; is why we didn&amp;rsquo;t use SCCM/Intune&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I Read the docs several times, and got to work following them were I needed to. I Selected what update packs we needed at the time, Windows Server 2012, Windows 10 etc.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I Put the computers into groups; Student desktops, Teacher Desktops, Laptops, Servers. As would make sense for our network at the time.&#xA;I Did a bit of testing on a couple of machines, Waited for all of the required update packages to download, and it worked as expected.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
