<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Minecraft on Quack Bot API Docs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Minecraft on Quack Bot API Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 12:01:51 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/minecraft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Spawn</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/spawn/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 16:25:52 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/spawn/index.html</guid>
      <description>Welcome to spawn, everyone who joins the server will see this when they join.
The Tower The bones of this building was my first project in the server after clearing an Area around spawn, to the top of the old build limit this has many floors for people to claim and put what they want.
Pride Robot A Nice rainbow Robot, first community project!
Aquarium The Aquarium (Closed For Maintenance) - Community Member Built</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexandria</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/alexandria/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 11:40:41 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/alexandria/index.html</guid>
      <description>The maze Just outside of Alexandria is the Maze and the Sheep
The Pyramid A Small Pyramid and its Cat friend
The Lighthouse of Alexandria </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Library Of Alexandria</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/library/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 11:45:28 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/library/index.html</guid>
      <description>A Wonderful Mega-build of a library / museum
Many hours and Many people went into this build.
The entrance with the lighthouse in the background
Grand Staircase A Staircase hidden away among the bookshelves
The Chandelier Art The Kitten Guards of the Library
A History of Armour and Fauna
The Vault a Near impenetrable vault to store the special books
The Books The Docks For those whom wish to arrive by boat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zone 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/newzone2024/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 12:01:51 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/newzone2024/index.html</guid>
      <description>We started a new survival play through in 2024, here is some of the stuff
Fishes House JJs House My House Auto Farms This has Cane, Bamboo, Kelp and a very awful smelter
New Theme Park Name TBD, Think something that makes Machland look tiny
With a treehouse Mega Farm 60k~ capacity
Over 300k Blocks moved
All in survival
Video coming soon ™</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dot</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/dot/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 11:58:58 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/dot/index.html</guid>
      <description>Not much to say here, the new build height tower was built in survival though&amp;hellip;
Apart from the super vault</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mach Land</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/machland/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 11:22:26 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/machland/index.html</guid>
      <description>Mach Land is rollercoaster park and entertainment zone..
Various community and group builds here.
Entrance and kids coaster Machyear blimp, fireworks &amp;amp; Space Mountain Collapsed Coaster A Failed baritone build, but it looks cool
Ride Entrances Mach Land Zoo A Short Rail (under construction) ride away from Machland is the Machland zoo, housed in a mega pyramid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Others</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/others/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 11:19:23 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/others/index.html</guid>
      <description>This is for impressive stand alone builds, where its 1/2 buildings not with an area around it of other things..
Zoo 1 The first zoo built in the server Dutch Government Building A Wonderful Build by Gorby
Dry dock TrapHouse A building worthy of its own page, but yet to be challenged so all you get it the outside</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JJs Towns</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/jjstowns/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 10:55:06 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/jjstowns/index.html</guid>
      <description>JJ Has many towns around and many one off mega builds, here are some of them that aren&amp;rsquo;t part of another area (or are there own distinct area)
Town 1 JJ&amp;rsquo;s 2/3 project, the first two have mainly been dismantled or rebuilt over time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trex Land</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/trexland/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 10:41:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/trexland/index.html</guid>
      <description>An Area a few blocks from spawn, containing mostly Trex&amp;rsquo;s /Related creations.
Rawr means i love you in dinosaur Dino art with the hotel in the background.
Trex&amp;rsquo;s House The Hotel A nice multi bedroom hotel at the top of a hill with a wonderful view and nearby rail connections
Mini Farm Just outside of trex land is a micro farm made by me, nothing special but quite pretty</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>