<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>QuackBot API on Quack Bot API Docs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in QuackBot API on Quack Bot API Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 12:01:51 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Print Adder V2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/printeradder/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/printeradder/index.html</guid>
      <description>Download PrinterAddV2.exe is a command line Click to Run file that will programmatically readd printers served from a print server to a set value!
This is useful for when group policy doesn&amp;rsquo;t correctly add printers (which is a common issue with complicated, many or large GPOs) or if you want to have a shortcut to add many printers at once if you don&amp;rsquo;t want to add printers via GPO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 12:01:51 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/minecraft/index.html</guid>
      <description>I Run a community Minecraft sever, over the 3 + Years we have made many builds. There will be a mix of community, Solo and mixed builds.
I think the server started Dec 2020 with people actually playing Jan 2021
It&amp;rsquo;s a mostly Vanilla Spigot sever, with a couple of minor mods such as a bookshelf and Dynamap.
The top players have many many hours combined, one of which has almost 60 days of playtime alone!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Botches and Bodges</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/whoops/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 22:18:45 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/whoops/index.html</guid>
      <description>Some stories of things going wrong, and the bodges that should never be talked about.
Most of this is going to cover my time as an IT Technician in a school..
A Mixture of working as a All around tech in one of the best schools in the county (T1 on paper but I Basically did everything from changing toner to VLans)
Then back to being a T1 Tech, this time in on of the biggest MATs in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FiveM Scripts Docs And Versions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/fivem/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/fivem/index.html</guid>
      <description>New FiveM Stuff.
currently moved to More FiveM
Machs Hunting | 0.0.6
MachsBD | 0.2.0
Machs Functions | 0.3.1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/powershell/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 20:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/powershell/index.html</guid>
      <description>Welcome to MACHS Scripts.
Here you will find a collection of scripts, mostly PowerShell, to help with Active directory management and other automation tasks.
These scripts, unless otherwise specified, and licensed under GNU Affero General Public License v3.0
&amp;ndash;
Tips ExecutionPolicy When running these scripts, you may need to run the following command in PowerShell.
This will allow you to run the script without a policy error.
You can also add this as a parameter when setting up scheduled tasks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>API V2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apiv2/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apiv2/index.html</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>API V3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apiv3/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apiv3/index.html</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>API V3 (Python)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apiv3_pythonbased/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apiv3_pythonbased/index.html</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Archives</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/thearchives/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 21:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/thearchives/index.html</guid>
      <description>A Collection of Old Sites and Projects.
Moved here as they no longer need to be there own site
TechGuyBlog I Started a blog type thing with a few tech stories, like news style, but it seems more sensible to merge it here.
dotRP_Docs The old Docs site for dotRP, contains the active docs for my FiveM Scripts</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>